Terms of use and privacy policy
===============================

Your use of our website is subject always to the following terms, which incorporate our privacy policy. By using our website, you accept these terms in full. If you disagree with any part of these terms, you may not use our website.

Who we are
----------

We are Campaign Against Antisemitism (CAA), the operators of this website, www.antisemitism.org. CAA is a volunteer-led charity dedicated to exposing and countering antisemitism through education and zero-tolerance enforcement of the law. We are a Charitable Incorporated Organisation registered with the Charity Commission for England and Wales (number 1163790). You can [contact us](https://antisemitism.org/contact/) through our website.

Collection, use and retention of information
--------------------------------------------

We obtain information about you when you use our website, for example, when you contact us to ask about antisemitism and our work to combat it, make a donation, apply to become a volunteer, or tell us about an antisemitic incident. The personal information we collect might include your name, address, telephone numbers, e-mail addresses, IP address, social media identifiers and information regarding what pages you accessed on our website, and when. If you make a donation online, your credit card or bank details are not held by us, they are collected by our third-party payment processors, who specialise in the secure online capture and processing of online transactions, as explained below.

We will use your information to promote human rights in relation to the elimination of antisemitism, including raising awareness of the occurrence of antisemitism and providing advocacy, assistance, care and relief in relation to those affected by antisemitism; advance education for the public benefit as regards the history, causes, effects and prevention of antisemitism; promote racial harmony for the public benefit between Jewish people wherever in the world and other members of society by the elimination of antisemitism; prevent or detect crime and/or apprehend or assist the prosecution of offenders; and provide a voluntary service, administer membership records, fundraise, process donations, promote the interests of the charity, fulfil any contractual obligations to you, manage our employees and volunteers, maintain our own accounts and records, seek your views on our work, notify you of changes to our services, send you other information that you have requested and that might be of interest to you and assist you in relation to any antisemitic incidents that you report to us.

We review how long we retain personal information for on a regular basis. We are legally required to hold some types of information to fulfil our statutory obligations (for example we are required to retain donation details to justify the collection of Gift Aid). We will hold your personal information on our systems for as long as is necessary for the relevant activity, or as long as is set out in any relevant contract that you hold with us.

Organisations are permitted to process personal information if they have a legal basis for doing so. We processes personal information mainly on the lawful basis of our legitimate interest (or those of a third party) in exposing and countering antisemitism through education and zero-tolerance enforcement of the law and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests. Other legal bases are: expressed and informed consent given by the person whose data is being processed; necessity in relation to a contract or agreement which the person has entered into or because the person has asked for something to be done so they can enter into a contract or agreement; legal obligation on us to process data. Children of any age have the same rights over the personal information processed about them as adults, although their ability to understand and to exercise these rights may vary depending on their age and capacity. We therefore ask those legally responsible for any children with whom we engage to understand that our obligations are to each of those children separately as individual data subjects and to work with us accordingly. Where we rely solely on consent as the basis for processing personal information, we are required to obtain your explicit consent and you can modify or withdraw this consent at any time by [contacting us](https://antisemitism.org/contact/), although this may affect the extent to which we are able to provide services to or interact with you in future.

We may change our policy from time to time and any such changes will be published on our website. You are advised to check from time to time that no changes have been made to any sections that are important to you. Notwithstanding any changes to this policy, we will continue to process your personal data in accordance with your rights and our obligations in law. We review how we process information on a regular basis.

Access to information
---------------------

We will not ever sell or rent your information to third parties.

We may pass your information to our third-party service providers, agents, subcontractors and other associated organisations for the purposes of completing tasks and providing services to you on our behalf (for example to process donations and send you e-mails). When we use third-party service providers, we disclose only the personal information that is necessary to deliver the service and we ensure that the terms of service require them to keep your information secure and not to use it for their own direct marketing purposes.

When you are using our secure online donation pages, your donation is processed by a third-party payment processor, which specialises in the secure online capture and processing of online transactions. If you have any questions regarding secure transactions, please [contact us](https://antisemitism.org/contact/).

When we are working on your behalf in connection with an antisemitic incident you may have witnessed or suffered, we may want to share your personal information with police, prosecutors, regulators, legal and other paralegal professionals. Where we do this, it is only with your express consent to share your personal information.

We may transfer your personal information to a third party as part of any restructuring or reorganisation of CAA, or if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal obligation or to enforce or apply our terms of use or to protect the rights, property or safety of our supporters, partners, volunteers or those we are helping. However, we will take steps with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

Choosing to receive information from us
---------------------------------------

You have a choice about whether or not you wish to receive information from us. If you do not want to receive communications from us about the vital work we do in combating antisemitism, our fundraising appeals and opportunities to support us, you can change your communication preferences by clicking on the link at the bottom of our e-mails and selecting your preferences by ticking the relevant boxes. Alternatively, you can change your preferences at any time by [contacting us](https://antisemitism.org/contact/).

Accessing and updating your information
---------------------------------------

The accuracy of your information is important to us. At the bottom of all of our update e-mails, you will find a link to access or change your information. Alternatively, if you change your e-mail address, or any of the other information we hold is inaccurate or out of date, please [contact us](https://antisemitism.org/contact/). You have the right to ask for a copy of the information that we hold about you. A small fee may be payable if an information request is particularly onerous. If we hold information about you, you have the right to be informed about the data we hold about you; access the information we hold about you; have your personal information corrected if it is incomplete or inaccurate; ask us to restrict how we process your information; and object to certain ways we use your information. In some circumstances, you may have a right to object to us processing your information. To see the rights available to you, please refer to the website of the Information Commissioner’s Office. If you want to raise a concern about how we have handled your information, you can make a complaint to us by [contacting us](https://antisemitism.org/contact/). You also have a right to complain to the Information Commissioner’s Office.

Information security
--------------------

When you give us personal information, we take steps to ensure that it is treated securely. Any sensitive information (such as credit or debit card details) is encrypted and protected using SSL. When you are on a secure page, a lock icon will appear on your internet browser.

However, when you e-mail is, that e-mail might be transmitted normally over the internet, which can never be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your information, we do our best to ensure that it is held securely on our systems. Where we have given (or where you have chosen) a password which enables you to access certain parts of our website, you are responsible for keeping that password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Profiling
---------

We may analyse your personal information to create a profile of your interests and preferences so that we can contact you with information relevant to you. We may make use of additional information about you when it is available from external sources to help us to do this effectively. We may also use your personal information to detect and reduce fraud and credit risk.

Cookies
-------

Our website uses cookies, small text files that are placed on your machine to store your preferences, store information for online processes, such as donation, and provide anonymised tracking data to third party applications that we use, such as Google Analytics. As a rule, cookies will make your browsing experience better. However, you may prefer to disable cookies on this website and on others. The most effective way to do this is to disable cookies in your browser. We suggest consulting the ‘Help’ section of your browser or taking a look at [About Cookies](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) which offers guidance for all modern browsers. Turning cookies off may result in a loss of functionality when using our website.

Rewards
-------

Where rewards are offered for information in criminal cases, the reward will be payable upon us determining, at our discretion, that there has been a successful conviction as a result of the information that you provided, and only after the deadline to appeal such a conviction has passed. If you contact the police directly and do not also contact us, you may be ineligible for the reward, given that we may be unable to contact you or determine that it was your information that led to the conviction.

Links to other websites
-----------------------

Our website contains links to other websites run by other organisations. We encourage you to read the privacy statements on the other websites that you visit. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and practices of other websites even if you access them using links from our website. Articles on this website may include embedded content (such as videos). Embedded content from other websites behaves in exactly the same way as though you had visited the other website. In addition, if you accessed our website from a third-party website, we cannot be responsible for the privacy policies and practices of the owners and operators of that third-party website and recommend that you check the policy of that third-party website.

Users aged 16 or under
----------------------

We wish to protect the privacy of children aged 16 or under. If you are aged 16 or under‚ please get your parent or guardian’s permission before providing us with personal information.

Transferring your information outside the EU
--------------------------------------------

As part of the services offered to you through this website, the information which you provide to us may be transferred to countries outside the European Union (EU). For example, this may happen if any of our servers are from time to time located in a country outside of the EU. These countries may not have similar data protection laws to the UK. By submitting your personal information, you are agreeing to this transfer, storage or processing. If we transfer your information outside of the EU, we will take steps to ensure that appropriate security measures are taken with the aim of ensuring that your privacy rights continue to be protected.

If you use our services while you are outside the EU, your information may be transferred outside the EU in order to provide you with those services.

Copyright
---------

Unless otherwise stated, CAA and/or our licensors own the intellectual property rights for all material on our website. All intellectual property rights are reserved. You may view and/or print pages from our website for your own personal use subject to restrictions set in these terms and conditions. You must not republish material from our website; sell, rent or sub-license material from our website; reproduce, duplicate or copy material from our website; or redistribute content from our website (unless content is specifically made for redistribution), other than by using the “share” buttons found on some pages of our website.

Disclaimer
----------

To the maximum extent permitted by law, we exclude all representations, warranties and conditions relating to our website and the use of this website (including, without limitation, any warranties implied by law in respect of satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose and/or the use of reasonable care and skill). Nothing in this disclaimer will limit or exclude our or your liability for death or personal injury resulting from negligence or fraud or fraudulent misrepresentation. We do not warrant or represent the completeness or accuracy of the information published on our website; that the material on the website is up to date; or that the website or any service on the website will remain available. To the extent that the website and the information and services on the website are provided free of charge, we will not be liable for any loss or damage of any nature. You should seek the advice of a professional adviser before acting on any information published on our website.

General
-------

We may revise these terms from time to time so please check this page occasionally to ensure that you are happy with any changes. These terms were last updated in May 2018. If a provision of these terms and conditions is determined by any court or other competent authority to be unlawful and/or unenforceable, the other provisions will continue in effect. If any unlawful and/or unenforceable provision of these terms and conditions would be lawful or enforceable if part of it were deleted, that part will be deemed to be deleted, and the rest of the provision will continue in effect. These terms create no rights or obligations enforceable by any third party. These terms constitute the entire agreement between you and us in relation to your use of our website and supersede all previous agreements between you and us in relation to your use of our website. These terms are governed by and construed in accordance with English law and any disputes relating to them are subject to the jurisdiction of the courts of England.

We are seeking to recruit [a General Counsel](https://antisemitism.org/jobs/general-counsel/) [a Paralegal](https://antisemitism.org/jobs/paralegal/) [a Video and Content Creator](https://antisemitism.org/jobs/video-and-content-creator/) [an Executive Assistant](https://antisemitism.org/jobs/executive-assistant/) to join our London office

Join the fight
--------------

[](https://antisemitism.org/act/#subscribe)Subscribe

[](https://antisemitism.org/act/volunteer)Volunteer

[](https://antisemitism.org/act/#donate)Donate

Campaign Against Antisemitism is a volunteer-led charity dedicated to exposing and countering antisemitism through education and zero-tolerance enforcement of the law. Everything that we do is done by people who volunteer their time, using donations contributed by members of the public. Join the fight against antisemitism by [**subscribing**](https://antisemitism.org/act/#subscribe) to our updates, [**volunteering**](https://antisemitism.org/act/#volunteer), or [**donating**](https://antisemitism.org/act/#donate%20style=).

**Justice, justice, you shall pursue - צדק צדק תרדף**  
© Copyright - Campaign Against Antisemitism, all rights reserved. Our logo is a registered trademark.  
Campaign Against Antisemitism is a charitable incorporated organisation registered with the Charity Commission (number 1163790).  
Use of our website is subject to our [terms](https://antisemitism.org/terms). Trees are planted every year to keep our work carbon neutral.

We use cookies to track use of our website and your preferences. Use of our website is subject to our terms of use and privacy policy.

### Cookie and Privacy Settings

How we use cookies

We may request cookies to be set on your device. We use cookies to let us know when you visit our websites, how you interact with us, to enrich your user experience, and to customize your relationship with our website.

Click on the different category headings to find out more. You can also change some of your preferences. Note that blocking some types of cookies may impact your experience on our websites and the services we are able to offer.

Essential Website Cookies

These cookies are strictly necessary to provide you with services available through our website and to use some of its features.

Because these cookies are strictly necessary to deliver the website, refusing them will have impact how our site functions. You always can block or delete cookies by changing your browser settings and force blocking all cookies on this website. But this will always prompt you to accept/refuse cookies when revisiting our site.

We fully respect if you want to refuse cookies but to avoid asking you again and again kindly allow us to store a cookie for that. You are free to opt out any time or opt in for other cookies to get a better experience. If you refuse cookies we will remove all set cookies in our domain.

We provide you with a list of stored cookies on your computer in our domain so you can check what we stored. Due to security reasons we are not able to show or modify cookies from other domains. You can check these in your browser security settings.

Check to enable permanent hiding of message bar and refuse all cookies if you do not opt in. We need 2 cookies to store this setting. Otherwise you will be prompted again when opening a new browser window or new a tab.

Click to enable/disable essential site cookies.

Google Analytics Cookies

These cookies collect information that is used either in aggregate form to help us understand how our website is being used or how effective our marketing campaigns are, or to help us customize our website and application for you in order to enhance your experience.

If you do not want that we track your visit to our site you can disable tracking in your browser here:

Click to enable/disable Google Analytics tracking.

Other external services

We also use different external services like Google Webfonts, Google Maps, and external Video providers. Since these providers may collect personal data like your IP address we allow you to block them here. Please be aware that this might heavily reduce the functionality and appearance of our site. Changes will take effect once you reload the page.

Google Webfont Settings:

Click to enable/disable Google Webfonts.

Google Map Settings:

Click to enable/disable Google Maps.

Google reCaptcha Settings:

Click to enable/disable Google reCaptcha.

Vimeo and Youtube video embeds:

Click to enable/disable video embeds.

Other cookies

The following cookies are also needed - You can choose if you want to allow them:

Click to enable/disable \_ga - Google Analytics Cookie.

Click to enable/disable \_gid - Google Analytics Cookie.

Click to enable/disable \_gat\_\* - Google Analytics Cookie.

Privacy Policy

You can read about our cookies and privacy settings in detail on our Privacy Policy Page.

×
